{
    "catergories":[
      "Vocabulary",
      "Iditarod Dream",
      "Random",
      "Mae Jemison",
      "Me, Mop, and Moondance",
      "Human Body Parts"
    ],
    "clueareaCol":[
      {
        "clueCol1":[
          {
            "question":"The definition of \"choreography\" is",
            "answer":"What is the art of arranging dance?",
            "options":[
              "What is the art of composing music?",
              "What is a lyrical dance?",
              "What is the art of arranging dance?"
            ],
            "value":100
          },
          {
            "question":"The word \"cramped\" is a?",
            "answer":"What is an adjective?",
            "options":["What is an adjective?","What is an noun?","What is an verb?"],
            "value":200
          },
          {
            "question":"To \"simulate\" something is to...",
            "answer":"What is to make something that feels or appears real?",
            "options":[
              "What is a duplicate/copy?",
              "What is to make something that feels or appears real?",
              "What is annoy or bother?"
            ],
            "value":300
          },
          {
            "question":"Which is NOT a synonym for \"straggle\"",
            "answer":"What is Step aside?",
            "options":["What is Step aside?","What is Fall behind?","What is Lag?"],
            "value":400
          },
          {
            "question":"Which of the following is a \"tributary\"",
            "answer":"What is US: Mississippi River?",
            "options":[
              "What is Korea: Han River?",
              "What is Canada: Hudson Bay?",
              "What is US: Mississippi River?"
            ],
            "value":500
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "clueCol2":[
          {
            "question":"Why doesn't Dusty see the snowmobile that causes his first tangle?",
            "answer":"Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the ice was slick so the dogs fell?",
              "Was it a moose so he was distracted?",
              "Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?"
            ],
            "value":100
          },
          {
            "question":"Why are rumors spreading that Dusty mistreated his dogs?",
            "answer":"Was it because he ran so fast?",
            "options":["Was it because his dogs look exhausted?","Was it because none of them are wearing their booties?","Was it because he ran so fast?"],
            "value":200
          },
          {
            "question":"Which part of the trail has Dusty never done before?",
            "answer":"Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the middle section of the forest?",
              "Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
              "Was it the end of the trail with the lake?"
            ],
            "value":300
          },
          {
            "question":"Which is NOT a difference between the real Iditarod and the Junior Iditarod?",
            "answer":"Was it both allow racers of all ages?",
            "options":["Was it both have different number of dogs in the teams?","Was it both allow racers of all ages?","Was it both start and finish in different parts of Alaska?"],
            "value":400
          },
          {
            "question":"At the beginning of the race, which is NOT a reason Dusty is on edge?",
            "answer":"Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
            "options":[
              "Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
              "Was it he's never done this part of the trail?",
              "Was it the trail was crowded with obstacles?"
            ],
            "value":500
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "clueCol3":[
          {
            "question":"Name the smallest country",
            "answer":"Where is Singapore?",
            "options":[
              "Where is New Zealand?",
              "Where is Singapore?",
              "Where is Jamaica?"
            ],
            "value":100
          },
          {
            "question":"Why are rumors spreading that Dusty mistreated his dogs?",
            "answer":"Was it because he ran so fast?",
            "options":["Was it because his dogs look exhausted?","Was it because none of them are wearing their booties?","Was it because he ran so fast?"],
            "value":200
          },
          {
            "question":"Which part of the trail has Dusty never done before?",
            "answer":"Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the middle section of the forest?",
              "Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
              "Was it the end of the trail with the lake?"
            ],
            "value":300
          },
          {
            "question":"Which is NOT a difference between the real Iditarod and the Junior Iditarod?",
            "answer":"Was it both allow racers of all ages?",
            "options":["Was it both have different number of dogs in the teams?","Was it both allow racers of all ages?","Was it both start and finish in different parts of Alaska?"],
            "value":400
          },
          {
            "question":"At the beginning of the race, which is NOT a reason Dusty is on edge?",
            "answer":"Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
            "options":[
              "Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
              "Was it he's never done this part of the trail?",
              "Was it the trail was crowded with obstacles?"
            ],
            "value":500
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "clueCol4":[
          {
            "question":"Why doesn't Dusty see the snowmobile that causes his first tangle?",
            "answer":"Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the ice was slick so the dogs fell?",
              "Was it a moose so he was distracted?",
              "Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?"
            ],
            "value":100
          },
          {
            "question":"Why are rumors spreading that Dusty mistreated his dogs?",
            "answer":"Was it because he ran so fast?",
            "options":["Was it because his dogs look exhausted?","Was it because none of them are wearing their booties?","Was it because he ran so fast?"],
            "value":200
          },
          {
            "question":"Which part of the trail has Dusty never done before?",
            "answer":"Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the middle section of the forest?",
              "Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
              "Was it the end of the trail with the lake?"
            ],
            "value":300
          },
          {
            "question":"Which is NOT a difference between the real Iditarod and the Junior Iditarod?",
            "answer":"Was it both allow racers of all ages?",
            "options":["Was it both have different number of dogs in the teams?","Was it both allow racers of all ages?","Was it both start and finish in different parts of Alaska?"],
            "value":400
          },
          {
            "question":"At the beginning of the race, which is NOT a reason Dusty is on edge?",
            "answer":"Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
            "options":[
              "Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
              "Was it he's never done this part of the trail?",
              "Was it the trail was crowded with obstacles?"
            ],
            "value":500
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "clueCol5":[
          {
            "question":"Why doesn't Dusty see the snowmobile that causes his first tangle?",
            "answer":"Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the ice was slick so the dogs fell?",
              "Was it a moose so he was distracted?",
              "Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?"
            ],
            "value":100
          },
          {
            "question":"Why are rumors spreading that Dusty mistreated his dogs?",
            "answer":"Was it because he ran so fast?",
            "options":["Was it because his dogs look exhausted?","Was it because none of them are wearing their booties?","Was it because he ran so fast?"],
            "value":200
          },
          {
            "question":"Which part of the trail has Dusty never done before?",
            "answer":"Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the middle section of the forest?",
              "Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
              "Was it the end of the trail with the lake?"
            ],
            "value":300
          },
          {
            "question":"Which is NOT a difference between the real Iditarod and the Junior Iditarod?",
            "answer":"Was it both allow racers of all ages?",
            "options":["Was it both have different number of dogs in the teams?","Was it both allow racers of all ages?","Was it both start and finish in different parts of Alaska?"],
            "value":400
          },
          {
            "question":"At the beginning of the race, which is NOT a reason Dusty is on edge?",
            "answer":"Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
            "options":[
              "Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
              "Was it he's never done this part of the trail?",
              "Was it the trail was crowded with obstacles?"
            ],
            "value":500
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "clueCol6":[
          {
            "question":"Why doesn't Dusty see the snowmobile that causes his first tangle?",
            "answer":"Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the ice was slick so the dogs fell?",
              "Was it a moose so he was distracted?",
              "Was it a blind corner, so he couldn't see it?"
            ],
            "value":100
          },
          {
            "question":"Why are rumors spreading that Dusty mistreated his dogs?",
            "answer":"Was it because he ran so fast?",
            "options":["Was it because his dogs look exhausted?","Was it because none of them are wearing their booties?","Was it because he ran so fast?"],
            "value":200
          },
          {
            "question":"Which part of the trail has Dusty never done before?",
            "answer":"Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
            "options":[
              "Was it the middle section of the forest?",
              "Was it the beginning section in the woods?",
              "Was it the end of the trail with the lake?"
            ],
            "value":300
          },
          {
            "question":"Which is NOT a difference between the real Iditarod and the Junior Iditarod?",
            "answer":"Was it both allow racers of all ages?",
            "options":["Was it both have different number of dogs in the teams?","Was it both allow racers of all ages?","Was it both start and finish in different parts of Alaska?"],
            "value":400
          },
          {
            "question":"At the beginning of the race, which is NOT a reason Dusty is on edge?",
            "answer":"Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
            "options":[
              "Was it he saw a moose on the trail?",
              "Was it he's never done this part of the trail?",
              "Was it the trail was crowded with obstacles?"
            ],
            "value":500
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }